var Question = require('./models').Question;

var createQuestions = function(id) {
/*---------- LEVEL 1, NOUNS ----------*/
	/* LESSON 1, Creatures of Essos */
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "havzi", "correctAnswer": "cat", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "zhavorsa", "correctAnswer": "dragon", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "hrazef", "correctAnswer": "horse", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "hlizif", "correctAnswer": "bear", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "adra", "correctAnswer": "turtle", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "dorvi", "correctAnswer": "goat", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "eshina", "correctAnswer": "fish", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "gezri", "correctAnswer": "snake", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "hrakkar", "correctAnswer": "lion", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "gimi", "correctAnswer": "mouse", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });

	/* LESSON 2, Nature and Landscapes*/
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "asavva", "correctAnswer": "sky", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "ashefa", "correctAnswer": "river", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "athasar", "correctAnswer": "wasteland", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "hranna", "correctAnswer": "grass", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "daeni", "correctAnswer": "leaf", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "dana", "correctAnswer": "forest clearing", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "ejakh", "correctAnswer": "river bank", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "fas", "correctAnswer": "cloud", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "feshith", "correctAnswer": "tree", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "halah", "correctAnswer": "flower", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });

	/* LESSON 3, Positions and Warfare */
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "vilajero", "correctAnswer": "battle", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "vov", "correctAnswer": "weapon", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "athvilajerar", "correctAnswer": "war", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "kohol", "correctAnswer": "bow", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "akkelenak", "correctAnswer": "leader", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "khal", "correctAnswer": "king", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "khaleesi", "correctAnswer": "queen", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "lajak", "correctAnswer": "warrior", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "lajasar", "correctAnswer": "army", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "najahheya", "correctAnswer": "victory", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });

	/* LESSON 4, Seasons and the Elements */
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "vorsaska", "correctAnswer": "summer", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "vorsa", "correctAnswer": "fire", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "chafka", "correctAnswer": "autumn", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "chaf", "correctAnswer": "wind", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "eyel", "correctAnswer": "rain", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "jesh", "correctAnswer": "ice", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "aheshke", "correctAnswer": "winter", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "ahesh", "correctAnswer": "snow", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "eveth", "correctAnswer": "water", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "eyelke", "correctAnswer": "spring", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });

	/* LESSON 5, Family */
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "inavva", "correctAnswer": "sister", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "ohara", "correctAnswer": "daughter", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "gaezo", "correctAnswer": "brother", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "janise", "correctAnswer": "niece", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "ave", "correctAnswer": "father", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "rizh", "correctAnswer": "son", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "kim", "correctAnswer": "ancestor", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "chiorikem", "correctAnswer": "wife", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "mai", "correctAnswer": "mother", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"userId": id, "prompt": "mahrazhkem", "correctAnswer": "husband", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });

/*---------- LEVEL 2, NUMBERS, PRONOUNS, AND INTERJECTIONS ----------*/
	/* LESSON 1, */
	/* LESSON 2, */
	/* LESSON 3, */
	/* LESSON 4, */
	/* LESSON 5, */

/*---------- LEVEL 3, ADJECTIVES AND ADVERBS ----------*/
	/* LESSON 1, */
	/* LESSON 2, */
	/* LESSON 3, */
	/* LESSON 4, */
	/* LESSON 5, */

/*---------- LEVEL 4, TRANSITIVE VERBS ----------*/
	/* LESSON 1, */
	/* LESSON 2, */
	/* LESSON 3, */
	/* LESSON 4, */
	/* LESSON 5, */

/*---------- LEVEL 5, INTRANSITIVE VERBS ----------*/
	/* LESSON 1, */
	/* LESSON 2, */
	/* LESSON 3, */
	/* LESSON 4, */
	/* LESSON 5, */
	
}

module.exports = createQuestions;